Guide to the R. Stuart Hummel Family Papers M1607
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Series I. STUART FAMILY PAPERS, 1874-1940
  - Subseries I. RACHEL ANNA GOLDEN STUART, 1880-1940
    - Rachel Anna Golden Stuart, biographical materials (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Rachel Anna Golden Stuart, biographical materials (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Rachel Anna Golden Stuart, biographical materials (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Rachel Anna Golden Stuart, biographical materials (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Rachel Anna Golden Stuart, Shanghai-Nanking Railway schedule, 1908 (Flat-box 9, Folder 1)
    - Rachel Anna Golden Stuart, album of pressed leaves, circa 1894-1900 (Flat-box 9, Volume 2)
  - Subseries II. GEORGE ARTHUR STUART, 1874-1911
    - George Arthur Stuart to family, miscellaneous (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - George Arthur Stuart to family, 1874-1896 (Box 10, Folder 2)
      - Letter 1 (Box 10, Folder 2, Item 1)
      - Letter 2 (Box 10, Folder 2, Item 2)
      - Letter 3 (Box 10, Folder 2, Item 3)
      - Letter 4 (Box 10, Folder 2, Item 4)
      - Letter 5 (Box 10, Folder 2, Item 5)
      - Letter 6 (Box 10, Folder 2, Item 6)
      - Letter 7 (Box 10, Folder 2, Item 7)
      - Letter 8 (Box 10, Folder 2, Item 8)
      - Letter 9 (Box 10, Folder 2, Item 9)
      - Letter 10 (Box 10, Folder 2, Item 10)
      - Letter 11 (Box 10, Folder 2, Item 11)
      - Letter 12 (Box 10, Folder 2, Item 12)
      - Letter 13 (Box 10, Folder 2, Item 13)
      - Letter 14 (Box 10, Folder 2, Item 14)
      - Letter 15 (Box 10, Folder 2, Item 15)
      - Letter 16 (Box 10, Folder 2, Item 16)
      - Letter 17 (Box 10, Folder 2, Item 17)
      - Letter 18 (Box 10, Folder 2, Item 18)
      - Letter 19 (Box 10, Folder 2, Item 19)
      - Letter 20 (Box 10, Folder 2, Item 20)
      - Letter 21 (Box 10, Folder 2, Item 21)
      - Letter 22 (Box 10, Folder 2, Item 22)
      - Letter 23 (Box 10, Folder 2, Item 23)
      - Letter 24 (Box 10, Folder 2, Item 24)
      - Letter 25 (Box 10, Folder 2, Item 25)
    - George Arthur Stuart to family, 1900-1905 (Box 10, Folder 3)
      - Letter 1 (Box 10, Folder 3, Item 1)
      - Letter 2 (Box 10, Folder 3, Item 2)
      - Letter 3 (Box 10, Folder 3, Item 3)
      - Letter 4 (Box 10, Folder 3, Item 4)
      - Letter 5 (Box 10, Folder 3, Item 5)
      - Letter 6 (Box 10, Folder 3, Item 6)
      - Letter 7 (Box 10, Folder 3, Item 7)
      - Letter 8 (Box 10, Folder 3, Item 8)
      - Letter 9 (Box 10, Folder 3, Item 9)
      - Letter 10 (Box 10, Folder 3, Item 10)
      - Letter 11 (Box 10, Folder 3, Item 11)
      - Letter 12 (Box 10, Folder 3, Item 12)
      - Letter 13 (Box 10, Folder 3, Item 13)
      - Letter 14 (Box 10, Folder 3, Item 14)
      - Letter 15 (Box 10, Folder 3, Item 15)
      - Letter 16 (Box 10, Folder 3, Item 16)
      - Letter 17 (Box 10, Folder 3, Item 17)
      - Letter 18 (Box 10, Folder 3, Item 18)
      - Letter 19 (Box 10, Folder 3, Item 19)
      - Letter 20 (Box 10, Folder 3, Item 20)
      - Letter 21 (Box 10, Folder 3, Item 21)
      - Letter 22 (Box 10, Folder 3, Item 22)
      - Letter 23 (Box 10, Folder 3, Item 23)
      - Letter 24 (Box 10, Folder 3, Item 24)
      - Letter 25 (Box 10, Folder 3, Item 25)
      - Letter 26 (Box 10, Folder 3, Item 26)
      - Letter 27 (Box 10, Folder 3, Item 27)
      - Letter 28 (Box 10, Folder 3, Item 28)
      - Letter 29 (Box 10, Folder 3, Item 29)
      - Letter 30 (Box 10, Folder 3, Item 30)
    - George Arthur Stuart to family, 1906-1909 (Box 10, Folder 4)
      - Letter 1 (Box 10, Folder 4, Item 1)
      - Letter 2 (Box 10, Folder 4, Item 2)
      - Letter 3 (Box 10, Folder 4, Item 3)
      - Letter 4 (Box 10, Folder 4, Item 4)
      - Letter 5 (Box 10, Folder 4, Item 5)
      - Letter 6 (Box 10, Folder 4, Item 6)
      - Letter 7 (Box 10, Folder 4, Item 7)
      - Letter 8 (Box 10, Folder 4, Item 8)
      - Letter 9 (Box 10, Folder 4, Item 9)
      - Letter 10 (Box 10, Folder 4, Item 10)
      - Letter 11 (Box 10, Folder 4, Item 11)
      - Letter 12 (Box 10, Folder 4, Item 12)
      - Letter 13 (Box 10, Folder 4, Item 13)
      - Letter 14 (Box 10, Folder 4, Item 14)
      - Letter 15 (Box 10, Folder 4, Item 15)
      - Letter 16 (Box 10, Folder 4, Item 16)
      - Letter 17 (Box 10, Folder 4, Item 17)
      - Letter 18 (Box 10, Folder 4, Item 18)
    - George Arthur Stuart, incoming correspondence, circa 1886-1911 (Box 10, Folder 5)
      - Letter 1 (Box 10, Folder 5, Item 1)
      - Letter 2 (Box 10, Folder 5, Item 2)
      - Letter 3 (Box 10, Folder 5, Item 3)
      - Letter 4 (Box 10, Folder 5, Item 4)
      - Letter 5 (Box 10, Folder 5, Item 5)
      - Letter 6 (Box 10, Folder 5, Item 6)
      - Letter 7 (Box 10, Folder 5, Item 7)
      - Letter 8 (Box 10, Folder 5, Item 8)
      - Letter 9 (Box 10, Folder 5, Item 9)
      - Letter 10 (Box 10, Folder 5, Item 10)
      - Letter 11 (Box 10, Folder 5, Item 11)
    - George Arthur Stuart and Methodist Episcopal Mission, correspondence, 1886-1899 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - George Arthur Stuart and Methodist Episcopal Mission, correspondence, 1900-1910 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - George Arthur Stuart and the University of Nanking (Box 10, Folder 8)
      - Letter 1 (Box 10, Folder 8, Item 1)
      - Letter 2 (Box 10, Folder 8, Item 2)
      - Letter 3 (Box 10, Folder 8, Item 3)
      - Letter 4 (Box 10, Folder 8, Item 4)
    - George Arthur Stuart and the University of Nanking (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - George Arthur Stuart, Chinese calling card, circa 1900 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - George A. Stuart, certificate of appointment as United States Vice Consul, Chinkiang, China, 1901 (Flat-box 250, Folder 1)
    - George Arthur Stuart, Bibles, circa 1880-1900 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - George Arthur Stuart and Wuhu General Hospital, 1887-1897 (Box 11, Folder 2)
      - Letter 1 (Box 11, Folder 2, Item 1)
      - Letter 2 (Box 11, Folder 2, Item 2)
      - Letter 3 (Box 11, Folder 2, Item 3)
      - Letter 4 (Box 11, Folder 2, Item 4)
    - George Arthur Stuart, autograph album: photocopies (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - George Arthur Stuart, Chinese Materia Medica: photocopy of 1911 edition (1 of 2). (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - George Arthur Stuart, Chinese Materia Medica: photocopy of 1911 edition (2 of 2). (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - George Arthur Stuart, Chinese Materia Medica, related correspondence (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - George Arthur Stuart, biographical materials (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - George Arthur Stuart, biographical materials (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - George Arthur Stuart, biographical materials (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - George Arthur Stuart, biographical materials (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - George Arthur Stuart, biographical materials (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - George Arthur Stuart, biographical materials (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - George Arthur Stuart, biographical materials (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - George Arthur Stuart, biographical materials (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - George Arthur Stuart, biographical materials (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - George Arthur Stuart, death certificate and related materials, 1911 (Box 13, Folder 1)
      - Letter 1 (Box 13, Folder 1, Item 1)
      - Letter 2 (Box 13, Folder 1, Item 2)
      - Letter 3 (Box 13, Folder 1, Item 3)
      - Letter 4 (Box 13, Folder 1, Item 4)
      - Letter 5 (Box 13, Folder 1, Item 5)
      - Letter 6 (Box 13, Folder 1, Item 6)
      - Letter 7 (Box 13, Folder 1, Item 7)
      - Letter 8 (Box 13, Folder 1, Item 8)
      - Letter 9 (Box 13, Folder 1, Item 9)
      - Letter 10 (Box 13, Folder 1, Item 10)
      - Letter 11 (Box 13, Folder 1, Item 11)
      - Letter 12 (Box 13, Folder 1, Item 12)
      - Letter 13 (Box 13, Folder 1, Item 13)
    - George Arthur Stuart, Simpson College diploma, 1906 (Flat-box 14, Folder 1)
    - George Arthur Stuart, scrapbook, volume I: photocopies, 1883-1884 (Flat-box 14, Folder 2)
    - George Arthur Stuart, scrapbook, volume II: photocopies, 1883-1884 (Flat-box 14, Folder 3)
  - Subseries III. ALCY ORMA STUART
    - Alcy Orma Stuart, outgoing correspondence, 1898-1905 (Box 15, Folder 1)
      - Letter 1 (Box 15, Folder 1, Item 1)
      - Letter 2 (Box 15, Folder 1, Item 2)
      - Letter 3 (Box 15, Folder 1, Item 3)
      - Letter 4 (Box 15, Folder 1, Item 4)
      - Letter 5 (Box 15, Folder 1, Item 5)
      - Letter 6 (Box 15, Folder 1, Item 6)
      - Letter 7 (Box 15, Folder 1, Item 7)
      - Letter 8 (Box 15, Folder 1, Item 8)
      - Letter 9 (Box 15, Folder 1, Item 9)
      - Letter 10 (Box 15, Folder 1, Item 10)
      - Letter 11 (Box 15, Folder 1, Item 11)
      - Letter 12 (Box 15, Folder 1, Item 12)
      - Letter 13 (Box 15, Folder 1, Item 13)
      - Letter 14 (Box 15, Folder 1, Item 14)
      - Letter 15 (Box 15, Folder 1, Item 15)
      - Letter 16 (Box 15, Folder 1, Item 16)
      - Letter 17 (Box 15, Folder 1, Item 17)
      - Letter 18 (Box 15, Folder 1, Item 18)
      - Letter 19 (Box 15, Folder 1, Item 19)
      - Letter 20 (Box 15, Folder 1, Item 20)
      - Letter 21 (Box 15, Folder 1, Item 21)
      - Letter 22 (Box 15, Folder 1, Item 22)
      - Letter 23 (Box 15, Folder 1, Item 23)
      - Letter 24 (Box 15, Folder 1, Item 24)
      - Letter 25 (Box 15, Folder 1, Item 25)
      - Letter 26 (Box 15, Folder 1, Item 26)
      - Letter 27 (Box 15, Folder 1, Item 27)
      - Letter 28 (Box 15, Folder 1, Item 28)
      - Letter 29 (Box 15, Folder 1, Item 29)
      - Letter 30 (Box 15, Folder 1, Item 30)
      - Letter 31 (Box 15, Folder 1, Item 31)
    - Alcy Orma Stuart, outgoing correspondence, 1906-1909 (Box 15, Folder 2)
      - Letter 1 (Box 15, Folder 2, Item 1)
      - Letter 2 (Box 15, Folder 2, Item 2)
      - Letter 3 (Box 15, Folder 2, Item 3)
      - Letter 4 (Box 15, Folder 2, Item 4)
      - Letter 5 (Box 15, Folder 2, Item 5)
      - Letter 6 (Box 15, Folder 2, Item 6)
      - Letter 7 (Box 15, Folder 2, Item 7)
      - Letter 8 (Box 15, Folder 2, Item 8)
      - Letter 9 (Box 15, Folder 2, Item 9)
      - Letter 10 (Box 15, Folder 2, Item 10)
      - Letter 11 (Box 15, Folder 2, Item 11)
      - Letter 12 (Box 15, Folder 2, Item 12)
      - Letter 13 (Box 15, Folder 2, Item 13)
      - Letter 14 (Box 15, Folder 2, Item 14)
      - Letter 15 (Box 15, Folder 2, Item 15)
      - Letter 16 (Box 15, Folder 2, Item 16)
      - Letter 17 (Box 15, Folder 2, Item 17)
      - Letter 18 (Box 15, Folder 2, Item 18)
      - Letter 19 (Box 15, Folder 2, Item 19)
      - Letter 20 (Box 15, Folder 2, Item 20)
      - Letter 21 (Box 15, Folder 2, Item 21)
      - Letter 22 (Box 15, Folder 2, Item 22)
      - Letter 23 (Box 15, Folder 2, Item 23)
      - Letter 24 (Box 15, Folder 2, Item 24)
    - Alcy Orma Stuart, outgoing correspondenceAlcy Orma Stuart, outgoing correspondence, 1911-1912 (Box 15, Folder 3)
      - Letter 1 (Box 15, Folder 3, Item 1)
      - Letter 2 (Box 15, Folder 3, Item 2)
      - Letter 3 (Box 15, Folder 3, Item 3)
      - Letter 4 (Box 15, Folder 3, Item 4)
      - Letter 5 (Box 15, Folder 3, Item 5)
      - Letter 6 (Box 15, Folder 3, Item 6)
      - Letter 7 (Box 15, Folder 3, Item 7)
      - Letter 8 (Box 15, Folder 3, Item 8)
      - Letter 9 (Box 15, Folder 3, Item 9)
      - Letter 10 (Box 15, Folder 3, Item 10)
      - Letter 11 (Box 15, Folder 3, Item 11)
      - Letter 12 (Box 15, Folder 3, Item 12)
      - Letter 13 (Box 15, Folder 3, Item 13)
      - Letter 14 (Box 15, Folder 3, Item 14)
      - Letter 15 (Box 15, Folder 3, Item 15)
      - Letter 16 (Box 15, Folder 3, Item 16)
      - Letter 17 (Box 15, Folder 3, Item 17)
      - Letter 18 (Box 15, Folder 3, Item 18)
      - Letter 19 (Box 15, Folder 3, Item 19)
    - Alcy Orma Stuart, outgoing correspondence, 1913 (Box 15, Folder 4)
      - Letter 1 (Box 15, Folder 4, Item 1)
      - Letter 2 (Box 15, Folder 4, Item 2)
      - Letter 3 (Box 15, Folder 4, Item 3)
      - Letter 4 (Box 15, Folder 4, Item 4)
      - Letter 5 (Box 15, Folder 4, Item 5)
      - Letter 6 (Box 15, Folder 4, Item 6)
      - Letter 7 (Box 15, Folder 4, Item 7)
      - Letter 8 (Box 15, Folder 4, Item 8)
      - Letter 9 (Box 15, Folder 4, Item 9)
    - Alcy Orma Stuart, outgoing correspondence, 1914 (Box 15, Folder 5)
      - Letter 1 (Box 15, Folder 5, Item 1)
      - Letter 2 (Box 15, Folder 5, Item 2)
      - Letter 3 (Box 15, Folder 5, Item 3)
      - Letter 4 (Box 15, Folder 5, Item 4)
      - Letter 5 (Box 15, Folder 5, Item 5)
      - Letter 6 (Box 15, Folder 5, Item 6)
      - Letter 7 (Box 15, Folder 5, Item 7)
      - Letter 8 (Box 15, Folder 5, Item 8)
      - Letter 9 (Box 15, Folder 5, Item 9)
    - Alcy Orma Stuart, outgoing correspondence, 1915-1917 (Box 15, Folder 6)
      - Letter 1 (Box 15, Folder 6, Item 1)
      - Letter 2 (Box 15, Folder 6, Item 2)
      - Letter 3 (Box 15, Folder 6, Item 3)
      - Letter 4 (Box 15, Folder 6, Item 4)
      - Letter 5 (Box 15, Folder 6, Item 5)
      - Letter 6 (Box 15, Folder 6, Item 6)
      - Letter 7 (Box 15, Folder 6, Item 7)
      - Letter 8 (Box 15, Folder 6, Item 8)
      - Letter 9 (Box 15, Folder 6, Item 9)
    - Alcy Orma Stuart, outgoing correspondence, 1918 (Box 15, Folder 7)
      - Letter 1 (Box 15, Folder 7, Item 1)
      - Letter 2 (Box 15, Folder 7, Item 2)
      - Letter 3 (Box 15, Folder 7, Item 3)
      - Letter 4 (Box 15, Folder 7, Item 4)
      - Letter 5 (Box 15, Folder 7, Item 5)
      - Letter 6 (Box 15, Folder 7, Item 6)
      - Letter 7 (Box 15, Folder 7, Item 7)
    - Alcy Orma Stuart, outgoing correspondence, 1919-1926 (Box 15, Folder 8)
      - Letter 1 (Box 15, Folder 8, Item 1)
      - Letter 2 (Box 15, Folder 8, Item 2)
      - Letter 3 (Box 15, Folder 8, Item 3)
      - Letter 4 (Box 15, Folder 8, Item 4)
    - Alcy Orma Stuart, incoming correspondence, circa 1900-1912 (Box 15, Folder 9)
      - Letter 1 (Box 15, Folder 9, Item 1)
      - Letter 2 (Box 15, Folder 9, Item 2)
      - Letter 3 (Box 15, Folder 9, Item 3)
      - Letter 4 (Box 15, Folder 9, Item 4)
      - Letter 5 (Box 15, Folder 9, Item 5)
      - Letter 6 (Box 15, Folder 9, Item 6)
      - Letter 7 (Box 15, Folder 9, Item 7)
      - Letter 8 (Box 15, Folder 9, Item 8)
      - Letter 9 (Box 15, Folder 9, Item 9)
      - Letter 10 (Box 15, Folder 9, Item 10)
      - Letter 11 (Box 15, Folder 9, Item 11)
      - Letter 12 (Box 15, Folder 9, Item 12)
      - Letter 13 (Box 15, Folder 9, Item 13)
      - Letter 14 (Box 15, Folder 9, Item 14)
      - Letter 15 (Box 15, Folder 9, Item 15)
      - Letter 16 (Box 15, Folder 9, Item 16)
      - Letter 17 (Box 15, Folder 9, Item 17)
    - Alcy Orma Stuart, miscellaneous, 1951-2007 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Alcy Orma Stuart, miscellaneous birth announcements (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Alcy Orma Stuart, biographical materials (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Otto D. Rasmussen, outgoing correspondence and miscellaneous, circa 1912-1930 (Box 16, Folder 4)
      - Letter 1 (Box 16, Folder 4, Item 1)
      - Letter 2 (Box 16, Folder 4, Item 2)
      - Letter 3 (Box 16, Folder 4, Item 3)
      - Letter 4 (Box 16, Folder 4, Item 4)
      - Letter 5 (Box 16, Folder 4, Item 5)
      - Letter 6 (Box 16, Folder 4, Item 6)
      - Letter 7 (Box 16, Folder 4, Item 7)
      - Letter 8 (Box 16, Folder 4, Item 8)
  - Subseries IV. ANNA MAY STUART
    - Anna May Stuart to Rachel Anna Golden Stuart, miscellaneous (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Anna May Stuart to Rachel Anna Golden Stuart, 1904-1913 (Box 16, Folder 6)
      - Letter 1 (Box 16, Folder 6, Item 1)
      - Letter 2 (Box 16, Folder 6, Item 2)
      - Letter 3 (Box 16, Folder 6, Item 3)
      - Letter 4 (Box 16, Folder 6, Item 4)
      - Letter 5 (Box 16, Folder 6, Item 5)
      - Letter 6 (Box 16, Folder 6, Item 6)
      - Letter 7 (Box 16, Folder 6, Item 7)
      - Letter 8 (Box 16, Folder 6, Item 8)
      - Letter 9 (Box 16, Folder 6, Item 9)
      - Letter 10 (Box 16, Folder 6, Item 10)
      - Letter 11 (Box 16, Folder 6, Item 11)
      - Letter 12 (Box 16, Folder 6, Item 12)
      - Letter 13 (Box 16, Folder 6, Item 13)
      - Letter 14 (Box 16, Folder 6, Item 14)
      - Letter 15 (Box 16, Folder 6, Item 15)
      - Letter 16 (Box 16, Folder 6, Item 16)
      - Letter 17 (Box 16, Folder 6, Item 17)
      - Letter 18 (Box 16, Folder 6, Item 18)
      - Letter 19 (Box 16, Folder 6, Item 19)
      - Letter 20 (Box 16, Folder 6, Item 20)
      - Letter 21 (Box 16, Folder 6, Item 21)
      - Letter 22 (Box 16, Folder 6, Item 22)
      - Letter 23 (Box 16, Folder 6, Item 23)
      - Letter 24 (Box 16, Folder 6, Item 24)
      - Letter 25 (Box 16, Folder 6, Item 25)
      - Letter 26 (Box 16, Folder 6, Item 26)
      - Letter 27 (Box 16, Folder 6, Item 27)
      - Letter 28 (Box 16, Folder 6, Item 28)
    - Anna May Stuart to Rachel Anna Golden Stuart, 1913 (Box 16, Folder 7)
      - Letter 1 (Box 16, Folder 7, Item 1)
      - Letter 2 (Box 16, Folder 7, Item 2)
      - Letter 3 (Box 16, Folder 7, Item 3)
      - Letter 4 (Box 16, Folder 7, Item 4)
      - Letter 5 (Box 16, Folder 7, Item 5)
      - Letter 6 (Box 16, Folder 7, Item 6)
      - Letter 7 (Box 16, Folder 7, Item 7)
      - Letter 8 (Box 16, Folder 7, Item 8)
      - Letter 9 (Box 16, Folder 7, Item 9)
      - Letter 10 (Box 16, Folder 7, Item 10)
      - Letter 11 (Box 16, Folder 7, Item 11)
      - Letter 12 (Box 16, Folder 7, Item 12)
      - Letter 13 (Box 16, Folder 7, Item 13)
      - Letter 14 (Box 16, Folder 7, Item 14)
      - Letter 15 (Box 16, Folder 7, Item 15)
      - Letter 16 (Box 16, Folder 7, Item 16)
      - Letter 17 (Box 16, Folder 7, Item 17)
      - Letter 18 (Box 16, Folder 7, Item 18)
      - Letter 19 (Box 16, Folder 7, Item 19)
    - Anna May Stuart to Rachel Anna Golden Stuart, 1914-1916 (Box 16, Folder 8)
      - Letter 1 (Box 16, Folder 8, Item 1)
      - Letter 2 (Box 16, Folder 8, Item 2)
      - Letter 3 (Box 16, Folder 8, Item 3)
      - Letter 4 (Box 16, Folder 8, Item 4)
      - Letter 5 (Box 16, Folder 8, Item 5)
      - Letter 6 (Box 16, Folder 8, Item 6)
      - Letter 7 (Box 16, Folder 8, Item 7)
      - Letter 8 (Box 16, Folder 8, Item 8)
      - Letter 9 (Box 16, Folder 8, Item 9)
      - Letter 10 (Box 16, Folder 8, Item 10)
      - Letter 11 (Box 16, Folder 8, Item 11)
    - Anna May Stuart to Rachel Anna Golden Stuart, 1916-1917 (Box 16, Folder 9)
      - Letter 1 (Box 16, Folder 9, Item 1)
      - Letter 2 (Box 16, Folder 9, Item 2)
      - Letter 3 (Box 16, Folder 9, Item 3)
      - Letter 4 (Box 16, Folder 9, Item 4)
      - Letter 5 (Box 16, Folder 9, Item 5)
      - Letter 6 (Box 16, Folder 9, Item 6)
      - Letter 7 (Box 16, Folder 9, Item 7)
      - Letter 8 (Box 16, Folder 9, Item 8)
      - Letter 9 (Box 16, Folder 9, Item 9)
      - Letter 10 (Box 16, Folder 9, Item 10)
      - Letter 11 (Box 16, Folder 9, Item 11)
      - Letter 12 (Box 16, Folder 9, Item 12)
      - Letter 13 (Box 16, Folder 9, Item 13)
      - Letter 14 (Box 16, Folder 9, Item 14)
      - Letter 15 (Box 16, Folder 9, Item 15)
      - Letter 16 (Box 16, Folder 9, Item 16)
      - Letter 17 (Box 16, Folder 9, Item 17)
    - Anna May Stuart to Rachel Anna Golden Stuart, 1918 (Box 16, Folder 10)
      - Letter 1 (Box 16, Folder 10, Item 1)
      - Letter 2 (Box 16, Folder 10, Item 2)
      - Letter 3 (Box 16, Folder 10, Item 3)
      - Letter 4 (Box 16, Folder 10, Item 4)
      - Letter 5 (Box 16, Folder 10, Item 5)
      - Letter 6 (Box 16, Folder 10, Item 6)
      - Letter 7 (Box 16, Folder 10, Item 7)
      - Letter 8 (Box 16, Folder 10, Item 8)
      - Letter 9 (Box 16, Folder 10, Item 9)
      - Letter 10 (Box 16, Folder 10, Item 10)
      - Letter 11 (Box 16, Folder 10, Item 11)
      - Letter 12 (Box 16, Folder 10, Item 12)
      - Letter 13 (Box 16, Folder 10, Item 13)
      - Letter 14 (Box 16, Folder 10, Item 14)
      - Letter 15 (Box 16, Folder 10, Item 15)
    - Anna May Stuart to Rachel Anna Golden Stuart, 1919-1920 (Box 17, Folder 1)
      - Letter 1 (Box 17, Folder 1, Item 1)
      - Letter 2 (Box 17, Folder 1, Item 2)
      - Letter 3 (Box 17, Folder 1, Item 3)
      - Letter 4 (Box 17, Folder 1, Item 4)
      - Letter 5 (Box 17, Folder 1, Item 5)
      - Letter 6 (Box 17, Folder 1, Item 6)
      - Letter 7 (Box 17, Folder 1, Item 7)
      - Letter 8 (Box 17, Folder 1, Item 8)
      - Letter 9 (Box 17, Folder 1, Item 9)
    - Anna May Stuart to Rachel Anna Golden Stuart, 1921-1924 (Box 17, Folder 2)
      - Letter 1 (Box 17, Folder 2, Item 1)
      - Letter 2 (Box 17, Folder 2, Item 2)
      - Letter 3 (Box 17, Folder 2, Item 3)
      - Letter 4 (Box 17, Folder 2, Item 4)
      - Letter 5 (Box 17, Folder 2, Item 5)
      - Letter 6 (Box 17, Folder 2, Item 6)
      - Letter 7 (Box 17, Folder 2, Item 7)
      - Letter 8 (Box 17, Folder 2, Item 8)
      - Letter 9 (Box 17, Folder 2, Item 9)
      - Letter 10 (Box 17, Folder 2, Item 10)
      - Letter 11 (Box 17, Folder 2, Item 11)
      - Letter 12 (Box 17, Folder 2, Item 12)
      - Letter 13 (Box 17, Folder 2, Item 13)
      - Letter 14 (Box 17, Folder 2, Item 14)
      - Letter 15 (Box 17, Folder 2, Item 15)
      - Letter 16 (Box 17, Folder 2, Item 16)
    - Anna May Stuart to Rachel Anna Golden Stuart, 1926-1929 (Box 17, Folder 3)
      - Letter 1 (Box 17, Folder 3, Item 1)
      - Letter 2 (Box 17, Folder 3, Item 2)
      - Letter 3 (Box 17, Folder 3, Item 3)
      - Letter 4 (Box 17, Folder 3, Item 4)
      - Letter 5 (Box 17, Folder 3, Item 5)
      - Letter 6 (Box 17, Folder 3, Item 6)
      - Letter 7 (Box 17, Folder 3, Item 7)
      - Letter 8 (Box 17, Folder 3, Item 8)
      - Letter 9 (Box 17, Folder 3, Item 9)
      - Letter 10 (Box 17, Folder 3, Item 10)
    - Anna May Stuart to Rachel Anna Golden Stuart, 1930-1937 (Box 17, Folder 4)
      - Letter 1 (Box 17, Folder 4, Item 1)
      - Letter 2 (Box 17, Folder 4, Item 2)
      - Letter 3 (Box 17, Folder 4, Item 3)
      - Letter 4 (Box 17, Folder 4, Item 4)
      - Letter 5 (Box 17, Folder 4, Item 5)
      - Letter 6 (Box 17, Folder 4, Item 6)
      - Letter 7 (Box 17, Folder 4, Item 7)
      - Letter 8 (Box 17, Folder 4, Item 8)
      - Letter 9 (Box 17, Folder 4, Item 9)
      - Letter 10 (Box 17, Folder 4, Item 10)
      - Letter 11 (Box 17, Folder 4, Item 11)
      - Letter 12 (Box 17, Folder 4, Item 12)
      - Letter 13 (Box 17, Folder 4, Item 13)
    - Anna May Stuart to Rachel Anna Golden Stuart, 1938-1939 (Box 17, Folder 5)
      - Letter 1 (Box 17, Folder 5, Item 1)
      - Letter 2 (Box 17, Folder 5, Item 2)
      - Letter 3 (Box 17, Folder 5, Item 3)
      - Letter 4 (Box 17, Folder 5, Item 4)
      - Letter 5 (Box 17, Folder 5, Item 5)
      - Letter 6 (Box 17, Folder 5, Item 6)
      - Letter 7 (Box 17, Folder 5, Item 7)
      - Letter 8 (Box 17, Folder 5, Item 8)
    - Anna May Stuart to siblings and others, 1903-1926 (Box 17, Folder 6)
      - Letter 1 (Box 17, Folder 6, Item 1)
      - Letter 2 (Box 17, Folder 6, Item 2)
      - Letter 3 (Box 17, Folder 6, Item 3)
      - Letter 4 (Box 17, Folder 6, Item 4)
      - Letter 5 (Box 17, Folder 6, Item 5)
      - Letter 6 (Box 17, Folder 6, Item 6)
      - Letter 7 (Box 17, Folder 6, Item 7)
      - Letter 8 (Box 17, Folder 6, Item 8)
      - Letter 9 (Box 17, Folder 6, Item 9)
      - Letter 10 (Box 17, Folder 6, Item 10)
      - Letter 11 (Box 17, Folder 6, Item 11)
      - Letter 12 (Box 17, Folder 6, Item 12)
      - Letter 13 (Box 17, Folder 6, Item 13)
      - Letter 14 (Box 17, Folder 6, Item 14)
      - Letter 15 (Box 17, Folder 6, Item 15)
      - Letter 16 (Box 17, Folder 6, Item 16)
      - Letter 17 (Box 17, Folder 6, Item 17)
      - Letter 18 (Box 17, Folder 6, Item 18)
      - Letter 19 (Box 17, Folder 6, Item 19)
      - Letter 20 (Box 17, Folder 6, Item 20)
      - Letter 21 (Box 17, Folder 6, Item 21)
      - Letter 22 (Box 17, Folder 6, Item 22)
      - Letter 23 (Box 17, Folder 6, Item 23)
      - Letter 24 (Box 17, Folder 6, Item 24)
      - Letter 25 (Box 17, Folder 6, Item 25)
      - Letter 26 (Box 17, Folder 6, Item 26)
      - Letter 27 (Box 17, Folder 6, Item 27)
      - Letter 28 (Box 17, Folder 6, Item 28)